Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Oversize
  - Series Title: The London Journal: and weekly record of literature, science, and art Series Number: vol. XLI, no. 1043-vol. XLIII, no. 1094 City: London Publisher: G. Vickers Format: hard cover Date: 1865-1866 (Box 163, Folder 2773)
  - Series Title: The London Journal: and weekly record of literature, science, and art Series Number: vol. XLIII, no. 1114-vol. XLVII, no. 1216 City: London Publisher: G. Vickers Format: hard cover Other Notes: incomplete Date: 1866-1868 (Box 163, Folder 2774)
  - Series Title: The London Journal: and weekly record of literature, science, and art Series Number: vol. LIII, no. 1352-LIV, no. 1398; vol. L, no. 1295-1298 City: London Publisher: G. Vickers Date: 1871, 1869 (Box 163, Folder 2775)
  - Series Title: The London Journal: and weekly record of literature, science, and art Series Number: vol. LIX, no. 1508-1533 City: London Publisher: G. Vickers Format: hard cover Date: 1874 (Box 163, Folder 2776)
  - Series Title: The Metropolitan Magazine City: New Haven Format: hard cover Other Notes: republished by Peck and Newton; bound with The Foreign Quarterly Review Date: 1834 (Box 164, Folder 2777)
  - Series Title: The Foreign Quarterly Review City: New Haven Format: hard cover Other Notes: republished by Peck and Newton; bound with The Metropolitan Magazine Date: 1834 (Box 164, Folder 2777)
  - Series Title: The Metropolitan Magazine City: New Haven Format: hard cover Other Notes: republished by Peck and Newton Date: 1835 (Box 164, Folder 2778)
  - Series Title: The New York Fireside Library Series Number: vol. VIII, no. 93-94, 97-101, 103-104 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Format: hard cover Date: 1881 (Box 164, Folder 2779)
  - Series Title: The New York Fireside Library Series Number: -109, 111-117 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Format: hard cover Date: 1881 (Box 164, Folder 2780)
  - Series Title: The New York Journal; an illustrated literary periodical Series Number: vol. I-II City: New York Publisher: P. D. Orvis Format: hard cover Date: August, 1853-June, 1854, 1853-1854 (Box 164, Folder 2781)
  - Series Title: The New York Journal; an illustrated literary periodical Series Number: vol. I City: New York Publisher: P. D. Orvis Format: hard cover Other Notes: incomplete Date: August, 1853-December, 1854, 1853-1854 (Box 164, Folder 2782)
  - Series Title: The Riverside Library Series Number: vol. I, no. 4, 10-11, 14-16, 21, 23-25, 27-29, 31-32, 34-36, 43-44, 46, 48-vol. II, no. 51-52, 56 City: New York Publisher: Norman L. Munro Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 164, Folder 2783)
  - Series Title: The Seaside Library Series Number: vol. XCII, no. 1861; vol. XXXV, no. 716; vol. LXXVI, no. 1533; vol. XCI, no. 1834; vol. XC, no. 1829-1830; vol. LXXXIX, no. 1797; vol. XL, no. 821; vol. XIX, no. 366; vol. XLV, no. 927; vol. LXV, no. 1320, 1330, 1323; vol. XXXVII, no. 787; vol. XXII, no. 433; vol. XXXIX, no. 794; vol. XLV, no. 914; vol. II, no. 40; vol. IV, no. 67; vol. LVII, no. 1166; vol. XI, no. 220; vol. XII, no. 234, vol. XCIII, no. 1871; vol. XIV, no. 279; vol. LXXXII, no. 1664; vol. LXXII, no. 1460; vol. LVII, no. 1167 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound with The Rose Library Date: 1877-1884 (Box 165, Folder 2784)
  - Series Title: The Rose Library Series Number: 46, 38, 37 City: Toronto Publisher: Rose Publishing Co. Format: hard cover Other Notes: bound with The Seaside Library Date: 1884 (Box 165, Folder 2784)
  - Series Title: Old Sleuth Library Series Number: vol. I, no. 1-20 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Format: hard cover Date: 1885 (Box 165, Folder 2785)
  - Series Title: Republic of Letters Series Number: 1-26 City: New York Publisher: William Pearson Format: hard cover Date: 1834 (Box 165, Folder 2786)
  - Series Title: The Republic of Letters; a weekly republication of standard literature Series Number: vol. II City: New York Publisher: George Dearborn Format: hard cover Date: 1835 (Box 165, Folder 2787)
  - Series Title: Reynolds's Miscellany of romance, general literature, science, and art Series Number: vol. XXII, no. 551-vol. XXIV, no. 603 City: New York Publisher: John Dicks Format: hard cover Date: 1859 (Box 165, Folder 2788)
  - Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: vol. II, no. 28; vol. IV, no. 66; vol. VII, no. 122-123; vol. VIII, no. 147, 150, 156; vol. IX, no. 170; vol. XI, no. 218; vol. XIV, no. 266; vol. XV, no. 293; vol. XVII, no. 340 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 165, Folder 2789)
  - Series Title: Seaside Library Series Number: vol. V, no. 92, 98; vol. VI, no. 101; vol. VII, no. 124; vol. XIII, no. 251; vol. XV, no. 288; vol. XXI, no. 407; vol. XXIII, no. 454; vol. XXV, no. 481-482, 504; vol. XXVII, no. 564; vol. XXXII, no. 661; vol. XXXIII, no. 683, 687 City: New York Publisher: George Munro Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 165, Folder 2790)
  - Series Title: Young Ladies of Great Britain Series Number: vol. III, no. 79-104 City: London Publisher: W. G. S. Urquhart Format: hard cover Date: 1870-1871 (Box 166, Folder 2791)
  - Series Title: Young Ladies of Great Britain Series Number: vol. IV, no. 112-vol. VI, no. 156 City: London Publisher: W. G. S. Urquhart Format: hard cover Date: 1871-1872 (Box 166, Folder 2792)
  - Series Title: The Lakeside Library Series Number: vol. I, no. 1-24 City: Chicago Publisher: Donnelley, Loyd & Co. Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 167, Folder 2793)
- Series VIII: Facsimile Reprints
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 1-3A Date: 1945 (Box 168, Folder 2794)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 4-6 Date: 1945 (Box 168, Folder 2795)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 7-10 Date: August-December, 1945 (Box 168, Folder 2796)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 11-14 Date: January-April, 1946 (Box 168, Folder 2797)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 15-18 Date: May-July, 1946 (Box 168, Folder 2798)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 19-22 Date: August-November, 1946 (Box 168, Folder 2799)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 23-26, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2800)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 27-30, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2801)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 31-34, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2802)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: nos. 35-38, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2803)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: unnumbered, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2804)
  - Title: Dime Novel Club Reprints Number: unnumbered, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2805)
  - Title: Happy Hours Brotherhood Reprints Number: nos. 8-12, 14 Date: 1947 (Box 168, Folder 2806)
- Series IX: Miscellany
  - Advertisements: Detective Fiction Weekly; Street & Smith, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2807)
    General note
  - Advertisement: Wood's Household Magazine, 1871 (Box 168, Folder 2808)
  - Advertisement: Harper's New Monthly Magazine, [1878] (Box 168, Folder 2809)
  - Article: "The Great Detective Team: Old and Young King Brady" by J. Edward Leithead (Box 168, Folder 2810)
    Has inscription from Leithead to Levy.
  - Catalogues: Arthur Westbrook Company; Gentleman's Magazine, 1840; Harper & Brothers November book-list, 1878 (Box 168, Folder 2811)
  - Catalogue: J.B. Lippincott & Co., 1876 (Box 168, Folder 2812)
  - Catalogues: Street & Smith, ca. 1926; 1932 (Box 168, Folder 2813)
  - Catalogues: Street & Smith Authors, nos. 11, 23, n.d.; 1913 (Box 168, Folder 2814)
  - Clippings: William J. Benners's Constance Library; Munro's list of Charles Garvice titles, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2815)
  - Manuscript: "The Matchless Nick Carter" by J. Edward Leithead, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2816)
  - Periodical: 19th Century Peep-Show, no. 19, 1944 (Box 168, Folder 2817)
    Includes reproduction of photograph of Laura Jean Libby.
  - Photograph: William J. Benners, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2818)